Clara E. Sipprell Papers
Clara E. Sipprell Papers
- Negatives and proof prints
  - O'Reilly, Mrs Gerald A. (Mrs. Buckley's daughter)
    - Negatives (Box FB047)
  - Orijo, Marcheso
    - Negatives (Box 54)
    - Negatives (Box FB047)
    - Negatives (Box FB168)
  - Osgood, Mr. Ed. G. (Daddy, Camp Nestobe)
    - Negatives (Box FB047)
  - Ostberg, Ragnar, 1938
    - Negatives (Box FB047)
  - Ostiomislensky [?]
    - Negatives (Box 54)
    - Negatives (Box FB048)
    - Negatives (Box FB168)
  - Ostro
    - Negatives (Box FB048)
  - Ouzonnoff, Paul, Oct 1937
    - Negatives (Box 54)
    - Negatives (Box FB048)
    - Negatives (Box FB131)
    - Negatives (Box FB197)
  - Ouzonnoff, T.O.
    - Negatives (Box FB168)
  - Owsley, Mrs. John E.
    - Negatives (Box FB048)
  - Oxford, NH
    - Negatives (Box FB131)
  - Paine, Mrs. Augustus (NYC), 1957
    - Negatives (Box FB048)
  - Painter, Mrs. Carl W., 1964
    - Negatives (Box FB048)
  - Palen, Curt
    - Negatives (Box FB131)
    - Negatives (Box FB132)
  - de Palencia, Mrs. Isabelle
    - Negatives (Box 54)
    - Negatives (Box 65)
    - Negatives (Box FB048)
  - Palmedo, Betty and Philip (children of Mrs. Roland Palmedo)
    - Negatives (Box FB048)
  - Palmedo, Mrs. Roland, 1941
    - Negatives (Box FB048)
  - Palmedo, Roland
    - Negatives (Box FB048)
  - Palmedo, Roland and Betsy
    - Negatives (Box FB048)
  - Palmedo, Roland and Betsy (children of Mrs. Roland Palmedo, 1185 Park Ave., SA 2-7422)
    - Negatives (Box FB048)
  - Palmer, Mrs. Bernard (321 South Garfield Ave., Jamesville, WI)
    - Negatives (Box 54)
    - Negatives (Box 65)
    - Negatives (Box FB168)
  - Pandit, Madame [Vijaya Lakshmi]
    - Negatives (Box 54)
    - Negatives (Box 65)
    - Negatives (Box FB048)
  - Pandit, Madame [Vijaya Lakshmi] (daughters Lekha, Tara, Rita)
    - Negatives (Box 54)
    - Negatives (Box FB048)
    - Negatives (Box FB160)
  - Parker, Eleanor, wedding (daughter of Mrs. Paul Revere Parker)
    - Negatives (Box FB048)
  - Parker, Mr. and Mrs. J. Russell
    - Negatives (Box FB048)
  - Parker, Mr. and Mrs. Kenneth (1000 Milwaukee Rd., Jamesville, WI)
    - Negatives (Box FB132)
  - Parker, Dr. P.R. [Paul Revere]
    - Negatives, 1959 (Box 53)
    - Negatives (Box FB048)
  - Parrish, Anne, 1944
    - Negatives (Box 54)
    - Negatives (Box FB168)
  - Parrish, Jean
    - Negatives (Box FB132)
  - Parrish, Maxfield
    - Negatives (Box 54)
    - Negatives (Box FB048)
    - Negatives (Box FB168)
  - Parsons, Mrs. William Usher
    - Negatives (Box FB132)
  - Patie, Angelo
    - Negatives (Box FB048)
  - Patterson, ----
    - Negatives (Box 54)
    - Negatives (Box 65)
    - Negatives (Box FB168)
    - Proof prints (Box 80)
  - Paul, Alice
    - Negatives (Box 54)
  - Paya, Mrs. Clara and children
    - Negatives (Box FB132)
  - Payne, Mary DeForest (son)
    See also DeForest, Mary Payne and children.
    - Negatives (Box FB132)
  - Peabody, Mrs. G.M.
    - Negatives (Box FB049)
  - Peattie
    - Negatives (Box FB132)
  - Peck, Anne
    - Negatives (Box FB132)
  - Peet, Mrs. Charles D.
    - Negatives (Box FB049)
  - Pendell Hill Quakers
    - Negatives (Box 54)
    - Negatives (Box FB049)
    - Negatives (Box FB168)
    - Proof prints (Box 80)
  - Penell, Mr. and Mrs.Lawrence, 1965
    - Negatives (Box FB049)
  - Percy, Ruth Scott
    - Negatives (Box FB049)
  - Perkins, ----
    - Negatives (Box FB133)
  - Perkins, Mrs. (of Haveshield)
    - Negatives (Box 54)
    - Negatives (Box 65)
    - Negatives (Box FB133)
    - Negatives (Box FB168)
  - Perkins, Mrs. Alice Knipland
    - Negatives (Box FB133)
  - Perkins, Dorothy
    - Negatives (Box 54)
    - Negatives (Box 65)
    - Negatives (Box FB133)
    - Negatives (Box FB168)
    - Negatives (Box FB169)
  - Perkins, Mrs. Enoch (son)
    - Negatives (Box FB133)
  - Perry, ---- (mother of Helen Perry Curtis)
    - Negatives (Box FB049)
    - Proof prints (Box 80)
  - Perry, Evelyn
    - Negatives (Box FB049)
  - Perry, Evie (daughter of Mrs. Henry Perry), 1943
    - Negatives (Box FB133)
  - Perry, Henry Jr.
    - Negatives (Box FB049)
  - Perry, Mrs. Henry and 2 children
    - Negatives (Box 54)
    - Negatives (Box FB049)
    - Negatives (Box FB169)
  - Perry, Phoebe
    - Negatives (Box FB049)
  - Perry, Polly and Annie (daughters? of Mrs. Henry Perry)
    - Negatives (Box FB133)
  - Perry, Mrs. Teneyk [Ten Eyck?]
    - Negatives (Box FB049)
  - Persons, Gladys, 1967
    - Negatives (Box FB049)
  - Peters, Jane (daughter of Mrs. F.K. Peters), Aug 1936
    - Negatives (Box 54)
    - Negatives (Box 65)
    - Negatives (Box FB133)
  - Peterson, Donald (2 children), 1936
    - Negatives (Box 54)
    - Negatives (Box 65)
    - Negatives (Box FB133)
  - Peterson, Mrs. Donald (Marishka, Lois)
    - Negatives (Box 54)
    - Negatives (Box 65)
    - Negatives (Box FB050)
    - Negatives (Box FB169)
  - Peterson, Mr. and Mrs. Jesse D.
    - Negatives (Box FB133)
  - Peterson, Jim (baby)
    - Negatives (Box FB049)
  - Peterson, Nell
    - Negatives (Box FB050)
  - Peterson, Rosicka and Solveig, 1944
    - Negatives (Box FB134)
  - Petri, Peter
    - Negatives (Box FB050)
  - Petrie, Pitt, 1958
    - Negatives (Box 54)
    - Negatives (Box 65)
    - Negatives (Box FB050)
    - Negatives (Box FB169)
  - Petrie, Mrs. Pitt, 1958
    - Negatives (Box FB050)
  - Pettingill, Dr. Samuel, 1958
    - Negatives (Box 54)
    - Negatives (Box 65)
    - Negatives (Box FB050)
    - Negatives (Box FB169)
  - Pfaelzer, Mrs. Franklin (202 Beacon St. Boston, MA)
    - Negatives (Box FB134)
  - Phillips, Duncan
    - Negatives (Box FB191)
  - Phillips, Duncan, collection of (Washington, DC), Marjorie Phillips
    - Negatives (Box 54)
    - Negatives (Box 65)
    - Negatives (Box FB191)
    - Negatives (Box FB200)
  - Phillips, Miss Edna
    - Negatives (Box FB050)
  - Phillips, Mrs. Elmer
    - Negatives (Box FB134)
  - Phillips, F.P.
    - Negatives (Box FB191)
  - Phillips, Freddy (garden)
    - Negatives (Box 54)
    - Negatives (Box FB169)
  - Piane, Rosy
    - Negatives (Box FB134)
  - Pickett, Clarence, 1957
    - Negatives (Box FB050)
  - Pickman, Mrs. Morgan (daughter)
    - Negatives (Box FB050)
  - Pier, Anne
    - Negatives (Box 54)
    - Negatives (Box FB134)
    - Negatives (Box FB169)
  - Pierce, Mrs. M.A.
    - Negatives (Box 54)
    - Negatives (Box FB134)
    - Negatives (Box FB169)
  - Pierson, Mrs. Charles E., 1959
    - Negatives (Box FB050)
  - Pitcher, A.M., 1956
    - Negatives (Box 54)
    - Negatives (Box 65)
    - Negatives (Box FB050)
    - Negatives (Box FB169)
  - Pitcher, Frances, 1967
    - Negatives (Box FB050)
  - Pleinkeet, Mrs. William and daughter Margaret
    - Negatives (Box FB050)
  - Plevitskaya, [Nadezhda] (Russian folk singer)
    - Negatives (Box FB051)
  - Plevitskaya, [Nadezhda]
    - Negatives (Box 54)
    - Negatives (Box FB050)
    - Negatives (Box FB153)
    - Negatives (Box FB169)
    - Negatives (Box FB191)
    - Negatives (Box FB199)
  - Plevitskaya, [Nadezhda], last sitting, 1927
    - Negatives (Box 54)
    - Negatives (Box 65)
    - Negatives (Box FB051)
    - Negatives (Box FB169)
  - Plumporter, Lars (son of Mrs. Mary Plumporter)
    - Negatives (Box FB134)
  - Poliakova, [Elena?]
    - Negatives (Box 54)
    - Negatives (Box FB191)
    - Negatives (Box FB200)
  - Popovic, ----
    - Negatives (Box 54)
    - Negatives (Box 65)
    - Negatives (Box FB051)
    - Negatives (Box FB169)
    - Negatives (Box FB170)
  - Porter, Mrs. Andrew
    - Negatives (Box FB191)
  - Porter, Mrs. H. (Holiday House)
    - Negatives (Box FB051)
  - Porter, Mrs. Henry (sons)
    - Negatives (Box 54)
    - Negatives (Box 65)
    - Negatives (Box FB170)
  - Porter, Ruggles and M. (tea party)
    - Negatives (Box FB140)
  - Powell, Mrs. Joe and twins
    - Negatives (Box FB051)
  - Powell, Nettie
    - Negatives (Box 54)
    - Negatives (Box 65)
    - Negatives (Box FB051)
    - Negatives (Box FB170)
  - Powell, Sue and Sally (twin daughters of J.W. Powell)
    - Negatives (Box FB051)
  - Powers, Mrs. (daughter)
    - Negatives (Box FB134)
  - Pratt, Mrs. George W.
    - Negatives (Box FB051)
  - Pratt, Marjory (mother), 1957
    - Negatives (Box FB051)
  - Pretie, Mrs. Angela
    - Negatives (Box FB134)
  - Price, Mr. and Mrs. Claire, 1958
    - Negatives (Box FB051)
  - Price, Mrs., 1957
    - Negatives (Box FB051)
  - Pullman, Mr. W.T. (daughter Candace, Mrs. T.K. Stevenson, grandmother, group of 3 children)
    - Negatives (Box 55)
    - Negatives (Box 65)
    - Negatives (Box FB051)
    - Negatives (Box FB170)
    - Proof prints (Box 80)
  - Quaker ladies (West Town)
    - Negatives (Box 55)
    - Negatives (Box FB170)
    - Proof prints (Box 80)
  - Quintal, Mrs. E.J.
    - Negatives (Box FB051)
  - Rachmaninoff, [Sergei]
    - Negatives (Box 55)
    - Negatives (Box FB191)
    - Negatives (Box FB200)
  - Radhakrishnan, Sir Sarvepalli
    - Negatives (Box 55)
    - Negatives (Box FB170)
  - Rao, Dr. Shiva
    - Negatives (Box 55)
    - Negatives (Box 65)
    - Negatives (Box FB135)
  - Rasmussen, Mr. and Mrs. George
    - Negatives (Box FB051)
  - Rathburn, Mrs. Lawrence W. (Dublin, NH)
    - Negatives (Box 55)
    - Negatives (Box 65)
    - Negatives (Box FB170)
  - Rau, Santha Rama, 1945
    - Negatives (Box 55)
    - Negatives (Box FB170)
  - Ream, Mr. and Mrs. Robert
    - Negatives (Box FB051)
  - Reed, Mr. and Mrs. Albert (son)
    - Negatives (Box FB051)
  - Reedy, Father and Mark Whalon
    - Negatives (Box 55)
    - Negatives (Box 65)
    - Negatives (Box FB135)
  - Reeves, Dr.
    - Negatives (Box FB051)
  - Reine, Bela, 1963
    - Negatives (Box FB052)
  - Reisinger, Dr. and Mrs. Paul B.
    - Negatives (Box FB135)
  - Renton
    - Negatives (Box FB052)
  - Reuss, Cohen
    - Negatives (Box FB135)
  - Reynolds, Jonathon (son of Mr. and Mrs. Henry Reynolds)
    - Negatives (Box 55)
    - Negatives (Box 65)
    - Negatives (Box FB052)
    - Negatives (Box FB170)
  - Rhee, Dr. Sigmund
    - Negatives (Box 55)
    - Negatives (Box FB170)
  - Rice, Chester T.
    - Negatives (Box FB135)
  - Richards, Dr. Charles
    - Negatives (Box 55)
    - Negatives (Box FB052)
    - Negatives (Box FB170)
  - Richards, Imogene and Billy
    - Negatives (Box FB052)
  - Richner, Thomas
    - Negatives (Box 55)
    - Negatives (Box 65)
    - Negatives (Box FB135)
  - Rienzi, Alexus
    - Negatives (Box 55)
    - Negatives (Box 65)
    - Negatives (Box FB052)
    - Negatives (Box FB170)
  - Rimsky, Dr. Natalie (Korsakov) [Natalia Rimskaya-Korsakova]
    - Negatives (Box FB052)
  - Rittenberg, Mrs. Sarah
    - Negatives (Box 55)
    - Negatives (Box 65)
    - Negatives (Box FB052)
  - Ritter, Mr. and Mrs. Burr H., 1957
    - Negatives (Box FB052)
  - Roberts, Frank
    - Negatives (Box 55)
    - Negatives (Box 65)
    - Negatives (Box FB052)
    - Negatives (Box FB170)
  - Robertson, Mr. Reuben B. (Hopewood, Flat Rock, NC, father of Mrs. Russell Norburn)
    - Negatives (Box 55)
    - Negatives (Box 65)
    - Negatives (Box FB052)
  - Rochester, Dr. and Mrs. Dudley (333 E, 30th Street, N.Y. 16 MV3-9166)
    - Negatives (Box FB052)
  - Rockefeller, Mr. John D. Jr.
    - Negatives (Box 55)
    - Negatives (Box 65)
    - Negatives (Box FB052)
    - Negatives (Box FB053)
  - Rockwell, Dr. Loula A. (142 Hillside Street, Asheville, NC)
    - Negatives (Box 55)
    - Negatives (Box 65)
    - Negatives (Box FB053)
  - Rocky Mountains
    - Negatives (Box 58)
    - Negatives (Box FB136)
    - Negatives (Box FB182)
  - Roebling, Mrs. John A.
    - Negatives (Box 55)
    - Negatives (Box 65)
    - Negatives (Box FB053)
    - Negatives (Box FB170)
  - Roerich, Nicolas [Nikolai Konstantinovich Rerikh]
    See also [Grebenshikoff?] Greteushikoff and Roerich.
    - Negatives (Box FB053)
  - Rollins, Mrs. H.M., 1958
    - Negatives (Box FB053)
  - Romanoff, ----, Dr.
    - Negatives (Box 55)
    - Negatives (Box 65)
    - Negatives (Box FB053)
    - Negatives (Box FB170)
  - Romany, Marie
    - Negatives (Box 55)
    - Negatives (Box 65)
    - Negatives (Box FB053)
    - Negatives (Box FB171)
  - Rome, etc.
    - Negatives (Box FB197)
  - Roosevelt, Eleanor
    - Negatives (Box 55)
    - Negatives (Box FB135)
    - Negatives (Box FB170)
  - Roosevelt, Mrs. Theodore [Edith]
    - Negatives (Box 55)
    - Negatives (Box 65)
    - Negatives (Box FB191)
  - Rosenberg, Mrs. S.A. (Hampton)
    - Negatives (Box FB053)
  - Roses, 1960; 1962
    See also Beyers and Roses.
    - Negatives (Box 55)
    - Negatives (Box 65)
    - Negatives (Box FB053)
    - Negatives (Box FB171)
  - Ross, Mr. and Mrs. Lawrence, 1967
    - Negatives (Box FB053)
  - Roth, Lindsay, 1943
    - Negatives (Box 55)
    - Negatives (Box 65)
    - Negatives (Box FB135)
  - Roth, Lois Kellogg
    - Negatives (Box 55)
    - Negatives (Box FB135)
    - Negatives (Box FB171)
  - Roy, Krishna
    - Negatives (Box 55)
    - Negatives (Box 65)
    - Negatives (Box FB135)
  - Rudhyar, Dane
    - Negatives (Box 55)
  - Rufus Jones' Bibles
    - Negatives (Box FB053)
  - Rust, ----
    - Negatives (Box FB053)
  - Rust, Mrs. Amasa (Saginaw), 1939
    - Negatives (Box 55)
    - Negatives (Box 66)
    - Negatives (Box FB135)
    - Negatives (Box FB171)
  - St. Denis, Ruth
    - Negatives (Box 57)
    - Negatives (Box FB171)
  - St. Seinon Island, Brunswick, Georgia
    - Negatives (Box 57)
    - Negatives (Box 66)
    - Negatives (Box FB138)
    - Negatives (Box FB171)
    - Negatives (Box FB172)
  - Sally, Antoinette
    - Negatives (Box FB136)
  - Sanborn, Mrs. George W.
    - Negatives (Box FB136)
  - Sanin, Alexander
    - Negatives (Box 55)
    - Negatives (Box 66)
    - Negatives (Box FB053)
    - Negatives (Box FB172)
  - Satterfield, Mrs.
    - Negatives (Box FB053)
  - Saunders, Mrs. (Miss Persons' friend), 1938
    - Negatives (Box FB053)
  - Saville, Mrs. Rodman (Susan, 7517 Riverview Way, Houston 42, TX)
    - Negatives (Box FB053)
  - Sawyer, Ruth
    - Negatives (Box FB136)
  - Saxe, Mr. John G.
    - Negatives (Box 55)
    - Negatives (Box 66)
  - Scarborough, Pauline
    - Negatives (Box FB136)
  - Schafress, Mrs. Harry [Henry?], 1941
    - Negatives (Box 55)
    - Negatives (Box 66)
    - Negatives (Box FB053)
    - Negatives (Box FB172)
  - Schauffler, Mrs. B.F.
    - Negatives (Box 55)
    - Negatives (Box 66)
    - Negatives (Box FB136)
    - Negatives (Box FB172)
  - Schilling, Miss Margery
    - Negatives (Box FB053)
  - Schmeckebier, Lawrence
    - Negatives (Box 55)
    - Negatives (Box FB172)
    - Negatives (Box FB181)
    - Negatives (Box FB202)
  - Schnelzer, Miss Katherine (Saginaw), 1939
    - Negatives (Box 55)
    - Negatives (Box 66)
    - Negatives (Box FB135)
    - Negatives (Box FB171)
  - Schnitnikoff, Helen, 1945
    - Negatives (Box FB136)
  - Schramm, Debbie, 1961
    - Negatives (Box FB053)
  - Schvetnikoff, Mrs.
    - Negatives (Box 55)
    - Negatives (Box FB054)
    - Negatives (Box FB173)
  - von Schwerin, Baron and Baroness Hares and family, Louise and Werner (Lund, Sweden)
    - Negatives (Box 55)
    - Negatives (Box 66)
    - Negatives (Box FB136)
    - Negatives (Box FB173)
  - Schwertzle, Jaquele (pianist), 1969
    - Negatives (Box FB054)
  - Schwimmer, Rosika
    - Negatives (Box 55)
    - Negatives (Box 66)
    - Negatives (Box FB172)
  - Scott, James
    - Negatives (Box 56)
    - Negatives (Box 66)
    - Negatives (Box FB054)
    - Negatives (Box FB172)
  - Scoville, Mrs. (granddaughter, Taconic, CT)
    - Negatives (Box 56)
    - Negatives (Box 66)
    - Negatives (Box FB173)
  - Scutter, Mr. snd Mrs. Nicolas, 1969
    - Negatives (Box FB054)
  - Seaton, Dr. Max Y., 1961
    - Negatives (Box FB054)
  - Seaton, Mrs. Max
    - Negatives (Box 61)
    - Negatives (Box FB054)
  - Seelye, Dr. Walter C. (Worcester, MA)
    - Negatives (Box 56)
    - Negatives (Box 66)
    - Negatives (Box FB173)
  - Seligman, Mrs.
    - Negatives (Box 56)
    - Negatives (Box 66)
    - Negatives (Box FB173)
  - Sellers, Clifford W.
    - Negatives (Box 56)
    - Negatives (Box 66)
    - Negatives (Box FB200)
  - Serkin, Rudolf, 1960
    - Negatives (Box FB054)
  - Sessions, Roga
    - Negatives (Box FB054)
  - Seveley, Mrs. Christopher
    - Negatives (Box FB054)
  - Shair, Ruth, 1963
    - Negatives (Box FB054)
  - Shannon, Grace (nephew, wife, and 2 children), 1966
    - Negatives (Box FB054)
  - Sharon, Miss, including tree
    - Negatives (Box FB055)
  - Sharpe, Mrs. William and children
    - Negatives (Box 56)
    - Negatives (Box 66)
    - Negatives (Box FB055)
    - Negatives (Box FB173)
  - Shelton Man Co.
    - Negatives (Box FB055)
  - Shields, Jane (daughter of Mr. Frances A. Shields)
    - Negatives (Box 56)
    - Negatives (Box 66)
    - Negatives (Box FB173)
    - Proof prints (Box 80)
  - Shih, Dr. Hu
    - Negatives (Box 56)
    - Negatives (Box 66)
    - Negatives (Box FB173)
  - Shik [?]
    - Negatives (Box FB055)
  - Shinn, Dr. James
    - Negatives (Box 56)
    - Negatives (Box 66)
    - Negatives (Box FB136)
    - Negatives (Box FB173)
  - Shoemaker, Rev. Sam
    - Negatives (Box 56)
    - Negatives (Box 66)
    - Negatives (Box FB136)
    - Negatives (Box FB173)
  - Shohet, Mrs. Harmon, 1958
    - Negatives (Box FB136)
  - Shokler, ----
    - Negatives (Box 56)
    - Negatives (Box 66)
    - Negatives (Box FB136)
    - Negatives (Box FB137)
    - Negatives (Box FB173)
    - Negatives (Box FB055)
  - Sidney Estate (Jenkins)
    - Negatives (Box 56)
    - Negatives (Box FB137)
    - Proof prints (Box 83)
  - Sikes, ----, 1957
    - Negatives (Box FB055)
  - Simonton, Ens. Edith
    - Negatives (Box 56)
    - Negatives (Box FB055)
    - Negatives (Box FB173)
  - Simpson, Mrs. Summer, Dec 1939
    - Negatives (Box 56)
    - Negatives (Box 66)
    - Negatives (Box FB173)
  - Sinclair, Mrs. Beverly Knowles (Swannanoa Road, Asheville, NC)
    - Negatives (Box 56)
    - Negatives (Box FB055)
    - Negatives (Box FB173)
  - Singer, French (Manchester)
    - Negatives (Box FB055)
  - Singh, J.J.
    - Negatives (Box 56)
  - Singleton, Lucile (nephew Alexander)
    - Negatives (Box FB191)
  - Sipprell, Allen, 1968
    - Negatives (Box 56)
    - Negatives (Box FB173)
  - Sipprell, Clara E.
    - Negatives (Box 56)
    - Negatives (Box 66)
    - Negatives (Box FB055)
    - Negatives (Box FB173)
    - Negatives (Box FB174)
    - Negatives (Box FB200)
  - Sipprell, Clara E., made by Cornelier Cummings, 1943
    - Negatives (Box 56)
    - Negatives (Box FB174)
  - [Sipprell, Clara E.] CES, very early glass
    - Glass plate negative (Box 69-01)
  - Sipprell, Clara E. and tomatoes
    - Negatives (Box 56)
    - Negatives (Box 66)
    - Negatives (Box FB174)
  - Sipprell, Clara E. (Paris)
    - Negatives (Box FB137)
    - Negatives (Box FB197)
  - Sipprell, Mr. F.J.
    - Negatives (Box 56)
    - Negatives (Box FB055)
    - Negatives (Box FB200)
    - Negatives (Box FB174)
  - Sipprell, Murray, 1970
    - Negatives (Box 56)
    - Negatives (Box 66)
    - Negatives (Box FB055)
    - Negatives (Box FB174)
  - Sipprell, W.J.
    - Negatives (Box FB137)
  - Skinner, Otis
    - Negatives (Box 56)
    - Negatives (Box 66)
    - Negatives (Box FB137)
  - Slaymaker
    - Negatives (Box FB137)
  - Sloan, John
    - Negatives (Box 56)
    - Negatives (Box 66)
    - Negatives (Box FB055)
    - Negatives (Box FB174)
  - Slocum, Jean
    - Negatives (Box FB056)
  - Smith, Dr.
    - Negatives (Box FB056)
  - Smith, Dr. (daughter)
    - Negatives (Box 56)
    - Negatives (Box 66)
    - Negatives (Box FB056)
    - Negatives (Box FB174)
    - Negatives (Box FB191)
    - Negatives (Box FB200)
  - Smith, Miss Beatrice Gordon
    - Negatives (Box 50)
    - Negatives (Box 64)
    - Negatives (Box FB056)
    - Negatives (Box FB174)
  - Smith, Chard, 1950
    - Negatives (Box FB056)
  - Smith, Mrs. E.C. (Bennington)
    - Negatives (Box 56)
    - Negatives (Box 66)
    - Negatives (Box FB056)
    - Negatives (Box FB174)
  - Smith, Mrs. Edward (St. Albans)
    - Negatives (Box 56)
    - Negatives (Box 66)
    - Negatives (Box FB056)
    - Negatives (Box FB174)
  - Smith, Mrs. G. Buchard
    - Negatives (Box FB137)
  - Smith, Mrs. Hicks and grandson
    - Negatives (Box 56)
    - Negatives (Box 66)
    - Negatives (Box FB174)
  - Smith, Marie (Norwalk)
    - Negatives (Box 56)
    - Negatives (Box 66)
    - Negatives (Box FB174)
  - Smith, Marie W. with dogs
    - Negatives (Box 56)
    - Negatives (Box 66)
    - Negatives (Box FB174)
  - Smith, Ross
    - Negatives (Box FB056)
  - Smith, Sarah, 1957
    - Negatives (Box FB056)
  - Snow, Edith H.
    - Negatives (Box 56)
    - Negatives (Box 66)
    - Negatives (Box FB056)
    - Negatives (Box FB174)
  - South Carolina, Charleston
    - Negatives (Box 56)
    - Negatives (Box FB137)
    - Negatives (Box FB138)
    - Negatives (Box FB152)
  - Spain, Frances Lander, 1959
    - Negatives (Box FB056)
  - Spargo, Mr. John
    - Negatives (Box 56)
    - Negatives (Box 66)
    - Negatives (Box FB056)
    - Negatives (Box FB175)
  - Speed, Mr. (Union Village)
    - Negatives (Box 56)
    - Negatives (Box FB138)
    - Negatives (Box FB175)
  - Sperry, Armstrong, 1963
    - Negatives (Box 56)
    - Negatives (Box 66)
    - Negatives (Box FB056)
    - Negatives (Box FB175)
  - Sprague, Mrs. Julian, May 1965
    - Negatives (Box FB056)
  - Sprague, Miss Ruth, 1956
    - Negatives (Box FB056)
  - Sprinkle, Placide, 1944
    - Negatives (Box 56)
    - Negatives (Box 66)
    - Negatives (Box FB175)
  - Sprinkler, Jaqueline
    - Negatives (Box 56)
    - Negatives (Box 66)
    - Negatives (Box FB056)
    - Negatives (Box FB175)
  - Stalin, Svetlana, 1969
    - Negatives (Box 57)
    - Negatives (Box FB176)
  - Stallings [Stalloys?], Miss Louise
    - Negatives (Box 57)
    - Negatives (Box FB197)
    - Negatives (Box FB200)
  - Stanislavsky, Constantin
    - Negatives (Box FB191)
  - Stanley, William
    - Negatives (Box 57)
    - Negatives (Box 66)
    - Negatives (Box FB176)
    - Negatives (Box FB138)
  - Stanton, Mr. John S.
    - Negatives (Box FB056)
  - Starr, Miss Josephine (213 Glenridge Ave., Montclair N.J.)
    - Negatives (Box FB138)
  - Steinert, Mr. and Mrs. Alan
    - Negatives (Box 57)
    - Negatives (Box 66)
    - Negatives (Box FB056)
    - Negatives (Box FB176)
  - Stevens, Mrs. Roger L. (daughter)
    - Negatives (Box 57)
    - Negatives (Box 66)
    - Negatives (Box FB056)
    - Negatives (Box FB176)
  - Stevenson, Mrs. T.K.
    - Negatives (Box FB138)
  - Stieglitz, Alfred
    - Negatives (Box 57)
    - Negatives (Box 66)
    - Negatives (Box FB138)
    - Negatives (Box FB139)
  - Still lifes
    - Negatives (Box 57)
    - Negatives (Box 66)
    - Negatives (Box FB056)
    - Negatives (Box FB057)
    - Negatives (Box FB139)
    - Negatives (Box FB140)
    - Negatives (Box FB175)
    - Negatives (Box FB176)
    - Negatives (Box FB191)
    - Negatives (Box FB192)
    - Negatives (Box FB193)
    - Negatives (Box FB197)
    - Negatives (Box FB200)
    - Negatives (Box FB201)
  - Still life, including "Still Life with St. Francis"
    - Negatives (Box FB057)
    - Negatives (Box FB193)
  - Still life, Yugoslavia
    - Negatives (Box FB140)
    - Negatives (Box FB197)
  - Still life for Phyllis
    - Negatives (Box 57)
    - Negatives (Box FB201)
    - Negatives (Box FB176)
  - Stillman, Charlotte
    - Proof prints (Box 80)
    - Proof prints (Box 0)
  - Stillman, Edgar Jr., 1942
    - Negatives (Box 57)
    - Negatives (Box 66)
    - Negatives (Box FB057)
    - Negatives (Box FB176)
  - Stillman, Lieut. Rufus C.
    - Negatives (Box 57)
    - Negatives (Box 66)
    - Negatives (Box FB057)
    - Negatives (Box FB177)
  - Stillman, Mrs. Rufus
    - Negatives (Box FB140)
  - Stoessler, Mrs. Sally
    - Negatives (Box 57)
    - Negatives (Box 66)
    - Negatives (Box FB058)
    - Negatives (Box FB177)
  - Stokowski, Mrs. L. [Leopold]
    - Negatives (Box 57)
    - Negatives (Box FB201)
    - Negatives (Box FB177)